<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tech Bytes Weekly</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tech Bytes Weekly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech News — Week 2 (Robots &amp; Regulations)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/week2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;week-2-robots-enter-the-home--governments-step-into-the-ai-arena&#34;&gt;Week 2: Robots Enter the Home &amp;amp; Governments Step Into the AI Arena&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-era-of-home-robotics-is-arriving-faster-than-expected&#34;&gt;The Era of Home Robotics Is Arriving Faster Than Expected&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the most significant announcements this week came from a major robotics manufacturer unveiling a prototype &lt;strong&gt;general-purpose home-assistant robot&lt;/strong&gt; — a device capable of folding laundry, loading dishwashers, and performing light household organization. While consumer-facing robots have existed before, most have been highly specialized (think: vacuum bots). This new entrant aims for a broader capability range: &lt;strong&gt;task planning + manipulation&lt;/strong&gt; rather than simple automation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech News — Week 1 (AI Chips &amp; Browser Wars)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-hugo-site/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;ai-hardware-heats-up--the-browser-wars-return&#34;&gt;AI Hardware Heats Up &amp;amp; The Browser Wars Return&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-wave-of-ai-chips-for-everyday-devices&#34;&gt;A New Wave of AI Chips for Everyday Devices&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The consumer AI race took a major step forward this week with &lt;strong&gt;NVIDIA&lt;/strong&gt; unveiling its newest low-power AI accelerator designed for laptops and lightweight workstations. Unlike its datacenter-focused GPUs, this chip targets &lt;strong&gt;on-device inference&lt;/strong&gt; — meaning more AI features can run locally without relying on the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This shift isn’t merely a performance jump — it’s a strategic redefining of &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; AI lives. For the past five years, the biggest breakthroughs depended on massive server clusters. Now, chipmakers are working to shrink those capabilities into ultraportable form factors. The move places NVIDIA into much more direct competition with &lt;strong&gt;Apple’s M-series neural engines&lt;/strong&gt;, which already dominate local AI on macOS devices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
